<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tutors@Seidenberg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">About</string>


    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="title_feedback">Feedback on app</string>
    <string name="title_available_plural">Available tutors right now</string>
    <string name="title_available_single">Available tutor right now</string>
    <string name="title_not_available">Sorry, no tutors available at this time</string>

    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="text_about">
        This app was created to demonstrate how beacons could help to display relevant information
        where it was needed; as in showing a notification (if bluetooth is activated) with the
        available tutors when entering the area where the tutors are. The app itself will
        always show the available tutors, or notify you if there are no tutors available.

        \n\nFor feedback or suggestions please use the feedback-button
        at the bottom of the screen.

        \n\nCreated by Jan Schøpp for Pace Mobile Labs.
    </string>
    <string name="title_howto">How to use</string>
    <string name="text_howto">
        To use the notification feature, just activate bluetooth and you will receive a
        notification with the available tutors, if you are in the Seidenberg Lounge. You don\'t
        need to have the app open to receive the notification, but if you are already within the
        space and have received the notification, you can always open the app
        to quickly check the availability of the tutors.

        \n\nIf notifications are not working even though you have bluetooth activated, please make
        sure you have given the app permission to use your location. This is needed to find out if
        you are in the Seidenberg Lounge.
    </string>

    <string name="tutor_Bhushan">Bhushan Surayawanshi/bs38923n@pace.edu</string>
    <string name="tutor_Ian">Ian Carvahlo/ic34882n@pace.edu</string>
    <string name="tutor_Jigar">Jigar Mehta/jm85438@pace.edu</string>
    <string name="tutor_Dhruvil">Dhruvil Gandhi/dg83196@pace.edu</string>
    <string name="tutor_Hardik">Hardik Patel/hp68381@pace.edu</string>

    <string-array
        name="tutor_strings">
        <item>Bhushan Surayawanshi/bs38923n@pace.edu</item>
        <item>Ian Carvahlo/ic34882n@pace.edu</item>
        <item>Jigar Mehta/jm85438@pace.edu</item>
        <item>Dhruvil Gandhi/dg83196@pace.edu</item>
        <item>Hardik Patel/hp68381@pace.edu</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="support_email">js45407n@pace.edu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rate_tutors">Rate Tutors</string>


</resources>
